{
  "1c": {
    "question": "The ATC system prevents a collision between aircraft operating in the system by applying separation between: ",
    "answer": "Aircraft and protected airspace",
    "choices": [
      "Aircraft and protected airspace",
      "Man made obstructrions on the ground",
      "Mountains",
      "Thunderstorms"
    ],
    "page": "3",
    "type": "multiple_choice"
  },
  "2c": {
    "question": "Define 'Separation'",
    "answer": "In air traffic control, the spacing of aircraft to achieve their safe and orderly movement in flight and while landing and taking off.",
    "choices": [
      "In air traffic control, the spacing of aircraft to achieve their safe and orderly movement in flight and while landing and taking off.",
      "The minimum longitudinal, lateral, or vertical distances by which aircraft are spaced through the application of air traffic control procedures.",
      "Separation between aircraft expressed in units of vertical distance.",
      "The fix, point, or location to which an aircraft is cleared when issued an air traffic clearance."
    ],
    "page": "3",
    "type": "multiple_choice"
  },
  "3c": {
    "question": "In what ways can aircraft be separated in BOTH radar and non-radar environments?",
    "answer": ["Vertically", "Laterally", "Longitudinally"],
    "choices": ["Vertically", "Laterally", "Longitudinally", "Visually", "Radar"],
    "page": "4",
    "type": "multiple_select"
  },
  "4c": {
    "question": "Define 'Separation Minima'",
    "answer": "The minimum longitudinal, lateral, or vertical distances by which aircraft are spaced through the application of air traffic control procedures.",
    "choices": [
      "In air traffic control, the spacing of aircraft to achieve their safe and orderly movement in flight and while landing and taking off.",
      "The minimum longitudinal, lateral, or vertical distances by which aircraft are spaced through the application of air traffic control procedures.",
      "Separation between aircraft expressed in units of vertical distance.",
      "The fix, point, or location to which an aircraft is cleared when issued an air traffic clearance."
    ],
    "page": "4",
    "type": "multiple_choice"
  },
  "5c": {
    "question": "Flight Level (FL): A level of constant atmospheric pressure related to a reference datum of how many inches of mercury?",
    "answer": "29.92",
    "choices": ["29.92", "28.82", "29.00", "29.29"],
    "page": "5",
    "type": "multiple_choice"
  },
  "6c": {
    "question": "At what altitude and above are all aircraft required to use the same altimeter setting?",
    "answer": "18,000 MSL",
    "choices": ["18,000 MSL", "1,800 MSL", "18,000 AGL", "180,000 MSL"],
    "page": "5",
    "type": "multiple_choice"
  },
  "7c": {
    "question": "Vertical separation minima are the same both Radar and Non-radar environments.",
    "answer": true,
    "choices": [true, false],
    "page": "6",
    "type": "multiple_choice"
  },
  "8c": {
    "question": "The minimum vertical separation required for non-RVSM equipped aircraft operating between FL180 and FL290 is",
    "answer": "1000ft",
    "choices": ["1000ft", "2000ft", "4000ft", "5000ft"],
    "page": "7",
    "type": "multiple_choice"
  },
  "9c": {
    "question": "Non-RVSM aircraft can be assigned an altitude between FL290 (inclusive) and FL410 as long as there is at least 2000ft of vertical separation.",
    "answer": false,
    "choices": [true, false],
    "page": "8",
    "type": "multiple_choice"
  },
  "10c": {
    "question": "All aircraft involved in a formation flight in RVSM airspace must be RVSM approved.",
    "answer": true,
    "choices": [true, false],
    "page": "8",
    "type": "multiple_choice"
  },
  "11c": {
    "question": "What type of separation consists of the spacing of aircraft at the same altitude by requiring operation on different routes or in different geographical locations?",
    "answer": "Lateral",
    "choices": ["Lateral", "Longitudinal", "Vertical", "Visual"],
    "page": "10",
    "type": "multiple_choice"
  },
  "12c": {
    "question": "Clearning aircraft to fly on different airways/routes whose widths or protected airspace do not overlap is a form of:",
    "answer": "Lateral Separation",
    "choices": ["Lateral Separation", "Vertical Separation", "Longitudinal Separation", "Horizontal Separation", "Visual Separation"],
    "page": "11",
    "type": "multiple_choice"
  },
  "13c": {
    "question": "Aircraft departing an airport with diverging headings of 30 degrees are considered laterally separated.",
    "answer": false,
    "choices": [true, false],
    "page": "12",
    "type": "multiple_choice"
  },
  "14c": {
    "question": "What is the standard non-radar longitudinal separation?",
    "answer": "10 minutes or 20 miles",
    "choices": ["10 minutes or 20 miles", "10 minutes or 5 miles, below FL600", "10 minutes or 10 miles", "20 minutes or 10 miles"],
    "page": "15",
    "type": "multiple_choice"
  }
}